Sidney Wilson

Professional Summary

Highly organized and versatile computer engineer with 4 years of experience in hardware maintenance and troubleshooting. Adaptable leader with an ability to work independently and with others, creating effective presentations, and developing opportunities that further establish organizational goals. Seeking to bring my skills and experience to a progressive organization with a positive and supportive culture where I can start and grow a career in Information Technology.

Technical Skills

- Visual Studio
- Computer Diagnostic and Repair
- AWS Cloud Management
- Data Processing

Interpersonal Skills

- Technical Communications
- Project Management
- Overcoming Objections
- Customer Service

Work History

Kitchen Service Lead

January, 2021 to Present

Amazon Fresh, Chicago, IL

- Improved long term strategies to develop a safer and efficient work environment.
- Working closely with management to retain our best practice image as a leading training site.
- Managing onboarding and training for new employees while modeling positive guidance and maintaining a safety environment, while keeping the customer's best interest.

Golf Assistant April, 2011 to 2021

Olympia Fields C.C., Olympia Fields, IL

- Coordinated events while creating an enjoyable and family-oriented environment amongst the membership.
- Nurtured and grew existing relationships by providing pristine service to future clients of the club.

Projects

Launched a powerful BGP based Site-to-Site VPN utilizing AWS

- Generated two secure environments allowing connectivity through IPSEC tunnels for each gateway.
- Adjoined FRR to the on-premises environment granting the BGP (Border Gateway Protocol).

Education & Certifications

AWS Data Protection & Disaster Recovery Specialist

September 2022

Food Handler Certification January 2021 to 2024

Bachelor of Science: Computer Engineering Milwaukee School of Engineering May, 2018